<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ROS Bag</string>
    <string name="title_activity_logs">Logs</string>
    <string name="help_text">
        "Runs the native Rosbag Record application that records data from ROS topics directly "
        "on the phone. For example, it could be useful if you want to save raw video stream that is "
        "otherwise impossible to transmit over the network. \n\n"

        "This app is free software and uses opensource Robot Operating System code of the ROS Bag package \n\n"

        "You can find description of the Rosbag Record here: http://wiki.ros.org/rosbag/Commandline#record \n\n"

        "The bags you record will be available on the filesystem. The exact location is the cache directory "
        "of this application. You can find the path in the very beginning of logs after the record was started. \n\n"

        "'Master URL' - set the master url. It should be in form of: http://localhost:11311 \n\n"

        "'Topics' - set to either record all available topic or only specific ones. In the latter case, "
        "specify the topics separated by comma. \n\n"

        "Additional arguments - the list of arguments that will be passed to the executable. For example, "
        " '--size 256 --lz4'. You can only pass the arguments that are supported by the Rosbag Record application. "
        "Here is the help message where you can find the list of supported arguments. \n\n"
        "-h, --help            show this help message and exit \n"
        "-a, --all             record all topics \n"
        "-e, --regex           match topics using regular expressions \n"
        "-x EXCLUDE_REGEX, --exclude=EXCLUDE_REGEX \n"
        "                      exclude topics matching the follow regular expression \n"
        "                      (subtracts from -a or regex) \n"
        "-q, --quiet           suppress console output \n"
        "-o PREFIX, --output-prefix=PREFIX \n"
        "                      prepend PREFIX to beginning of bag name (name will \n"
        "                      always end with date stamp) \n"
        "-O NAME, --output-name=NAME \n"
        "                      record to bag with name NAME.bag \n"
        "--split               split the bag when maximum size or duration is reached \n"
        "--size=SIZE           record a bag of maximum size SIZE MB. (Default: \n"
        "                      infinite) \n"
        "--duration=DURATION   record a bag of maximum duration DURATION in seconds, \n"
        "                      unless 'm', or 'h' is appended. \n"
        "-b SIZE, --buffsize=SIZE \n"
        "                      use an internal buffer of SIZE MB (Default: 256, 0 = \n"
        "                      infinite) \n"
        "--chunksize=SIZE      Advanced. Record to chunks of SIZE KB (Default: 768) \n"
        "-l NUM, --limit=NUM   only record NUM messages on each topic \n"
        "--node=NODE           record all topics subscribed to by a specific node \n"
        "-j, --bz2             use BZ2 compression \n"
        "--lz4                 use LZ4 compression \n\n"

        "You can always see the command line with the executable and arguments in logs "
        "to understand how you run the application \n\n"

        "'Additional environment variables' - comma separated list of key value pairs. For example, "
        "'MYVAR=1,OTHERVAR=abc'. They will be set in addition to those that are set by default. Those "
        "are: ROS_MASTER_URI, HOME. You can override the default environment variables, but please "
        "note that the ROS_MASTER_URI is changed by the 'Master URL' field.\n"
        "You can escape comma in key or value with \\, if needed\n\n"

        "'Start record' launches the executable. \n\n"

        "'Show output' shows the output from both stdout and stderr of the running executable. \n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">preference_file</string>
</resources>
